

Personal Information

Kliment Malenko

Skopje, Macedonia

Phone: +38978334194 klimentoh@hotmail.com

Web Developer / WordPress Developer / Team Leader

Excellent in the area of Web Development, profound knowledge in WordPress. Currently working at Digicube as a team leader and WordPress developer.

I have 4 years experience as a Web Developer. Worked 1 year as a PHP developer, then continued as a WordPress developer. Building themes from scratch and modifying as well as plugins.

Skills

- WordPress
- ♣ PHP
- MySQL
- JavaScript, jQuery
- ♣ HTML5
- CSS3
- Software Project Management
- Zend Framework

Professional Experience

Ш	Team Leader/Mentor/WordPress Developer at Digicube AG (Marketing and Advertising)
	Jan 2019 – present	

WordPress Developer at SoPro (Marketing and Advertising) - helps businesses to identify and
engage with qualified prospects.
Nov 2016 – Jan 2019

☐ PHP Intern at "Quantoo sp. z o.o." - Krakow, Poland Dec 2015 - April 2016

Volunteer work as a computer assistant at "General Hospital"

- Ohrid. Sep 2015 - Oct 2015

• Intern at "Jongis Doo" in Ohrid, Macedonia a big software development company.

Jun 2013 - Aug 2013

Jun 2014 - Aug 2014

• Junior developer at "Mikroplus Doo" in Ohrid, Macedonia, a young software development company.

July 2012 - Aug 2012

Education

- ♣ I am currently pursuing Master's degree in Bioinformatics AT FACULTY OF COMPUTER SCIENCE & ENGINEERING, Skopje
- * ST. PAUL THE APOSTLE UNIVERSITY, Ohrid
- * FACULTY OF COMPUTER AND INFORMATION SCIENCE, Ljubljana

ACQUIRED TITLE - Bachelor of Science in Information Science and Technology in the field of Communication Networks and Security (VII/1 - 240 ECTS)

 λ Major: Communication and Network security

Additional activities, awards and honors

- Active member of IAESTE Macedonia organization for exchange students for gaining technical experience.
- Member in project "Cracking wireless network with WPA/WPA2 encryption andenhanced protection" – 2015
- Built web application for a project called "Quest for Power" 2015, a simple strategy game.
- Participant in programming contest "Codefest" 2013, held in UIST.
- Ex-member in chess club held in UIST. Also won third place award 2013

Languages

Macedonian –Native English - C1 German - A2 Serbo-Croatian – C1 Bulgarian - B2

Levels: A1/2: Basic user - B1/2: Independent user - C1/2 Proficient user